<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Products &#8211; CR Wellness Dispensary</title>
	<atom:link href="/shop/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2018 09:42:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Muscle Rub 70ml/250mg</title>
		<link>/product/muscle-rub-70ml-250mg/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2018 06:22:31 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[root]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product&#038;p=857</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Our Muscle Rub is formulated with soothing analgesic essential oils in combination with Cannabis, CBD and Arnica to ease aches and pains and promote a cooling effect to applied areas.

Ingredients:

Organic Coconut Oil, Cannabis, Arnica, Shea Butter, CBD, essential oils of Wintergreen, Peppermint, Eucalyptus, Camphor, Black Pepper, Lavender and Nutmeg.

Available in:]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img src='-content/uploads/2018/04/MuscleRubTrio.jpg'></p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cannabis Salve 70ml stick: 250mg</title>
		<link>/product/cannabis-salve-70ml-stick-250mg/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2018 06:21:20 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[root]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product&#038;p=855</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[This healing salve is a powerful topical that may be used as an anti-inflammatory to ease aches and pains while also soothing skin irritations. Enjoy deep relief without the psychoactive effect of cannabis. We carefully blend the infusion with other herbs to offer a unique salve that works on many levels. Common uses include arthritis, psoriasis, eczema, burns, rashes, anti-wrinkle, scar prevention, skin cell regeneration, sun spots, tattoo healing and to ease menstrual cramps, insomnia, migraines &#038; headaches.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img src='-content/uploads/2018/04/Salve30ml-1.jpg'></p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Natural Terpene Infused Lavender Soap</title>
		<link>/product/100-all-natural-relax-lavender-soap/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2018 06:20:05 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[root]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product&#038;p=852</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[These handcrafted all natural organic soaps are made with the highest quality ingredients. Each bar is infused with Hemp Terpenes &#038; essential oils for medical purposes.

Discover the Amazing Benefits of this Natural Soap Infused with Hemp Oil and Hemp Terpenes

Hemp Oil is one of the world’s richest sources of polyunsaturated fats while also including two of the important essential fatty acids Omega 3 and Omega 6, and gamma-linolenic acid. These fatty acids are essential in helping maintain the natural moisture content in the body, and because of this, it acts as a good moisturizing agent for the skin. Hemp not only prevents the drying out of the skin, but it is also a rich source of Vitamin D and one begins to wonder why so little focus is provided to this wonderful option in skin care!H Hemp Oil is both moisturizing and penetrating, which helps increase its value when one is looking to add it to whole body care.

These benefits arise from the simple recognition that hemp contains three times more Omega-3 fatty acids than it does of the Omega-6. This is such an important point since Omega-3s are recognized for the anti-inflammatory benefits offered. By applying this to the skin in the form of soap, the fatty acids work to ease the inflammation caused by acne and even slow down the oxidation of free radicals, which in turn help the skin appear more healthy and youthful.

UNDERSTANDING HOW HEMP SOAPS REDUCES THE SIGNS OF AGING

One of the things many fail to realize is that as we age, the metabolism of our cells decrease and as a result, there is a reduction of essential fatty acids which are ingested that will be released into the epidermis (or the topmost layer of the skin). As a result, our skin becomes thinner and extremely dry. This age-related decline attributes to the formation of wrinkles and even the overall appearance of aged skin. The application of hemp oil through body care products, such as soaps and lotions, will compensate for the decline and minimize the signs of aging.

Buy Cannabis Infused Products Onlin]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img src='-content/uploads/2018/04/Relax-Lavander.gif'></p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Purple Syrup Tincture (Headstash)</title>
		<link>/product/purple-syrup-tincture-headstash/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 01:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[root]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost/product/import-placeholder-for-383/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Add the <strong>P</strong><strong>urple Syrup Tincture</strong> elixir to carbonated water or your favourite clear soda/ beverage, and wait up to an hour before consuming more of the elixir.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img src='http://localhost/wp-content/uploads/2018/03/38537_headstash_clearlymedicinal_seedsmanhazeshatter_1_1_-768x768.jpg'></p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Grape Syrup (60ml) (Thompson Caribou)</title>
		<link>/product/grape-syrup-60ml-thompson-caribou/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 01:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[root]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost/product/import-placeholder-for-381/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[1 Gram of Premium Concentrates in every 50ml! That’s 1000mg of THC infused into an all Natural Grape Syrup. Drink Your Dabs, Mix it with your favorite Soda/Pop !]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img src='http://localhost/wp-content/uploads/2018/03/Thompsoncaribougrape.jpg'></p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mota Iced Tea Mix 150mg</title>
		<link>/product/mota-iced-tea-mix-150mg/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 01:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[root]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost/product/import-placeholder-for-379/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[You don’t need to master croquet to learn this simple bit of ye olde English lifestyle lore: on a hot summer’s day — or anytime thirst needs refreshing— iced tea is <em>the </em>nice tea. Our medicated iced tea blends citrus and tea flavours with a well-balanced splash of sugar sweetness. Just add water and serve over ice. Ahhh. And our medicated, cannabis infused quencher comes through, with a consistent measured dose of THC.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img src='http://localhost/wp-content/uploads/2018/03/mota-iced-tea-mix-front-from-herb-approach.jpg'></p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Herb Approach Baked Rice Crispy Squares 60mg</title>
		<link>/product/herb-approach-baked-rice-crispy-squares-60mg/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 01:16:08 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[root]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost/product/import-placeholder-for-377/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Ooey-gooey, crispy and crunchy. A delightful twist on a delicious classic. <strong>Rice Crispy</strong> folded into melted marshmallow. And just when you thought it couldn’t get any better, we added a decadent layer of chocolate on top… hungry yet?]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img src='http://localhost/wp-content/uploads/2018/03/herbapproach-baked-edibles-rice-crispy-squares.jpg'></p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mota Medicated Peanut Butter Square 150mg</title>
		<link>/product/mota-medicated-peanut-butter-square-150mg/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 01:16:07 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[root]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost/product/import-placeholder-for-375/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[The magic of peanut butter, marshmallows, butter and vanilla infused with a measured dose of 150mg THC makes this great North American square a viable option for chronic pain, insomnia, and stress. Each order includes one square.

&#160;]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img src='http://localhost/wp-content/uploads/2018/03/mota-medicated-peanut-butter-square-150mg-thc-from-herb-approach.jpg'></p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>MOTA Dried Mango</title>
		<link>/product/mota-dried-mango/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 01:16:07 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[root]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost/product/import-placeholder-for-373/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Cannabis infused dried mango, coming from one of Canada’s leading companies, MOTA, is made to keep you medicated. Each bag guaranteed to please with 150mg of THC, and made with natural ingredients (including MOTA’s signature THC juice) these dried pieces of the tropics are the healthiest way to medicate.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img src='-content/uploads/2018/03/Mota-Dried-Mango-600x600.jpg'></p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Apothecary 20mg THC Oil</title>
		<link>/product/apothecary-20mg-thc-oil/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 01:16:06 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[root]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost/product/import-placeholder-for-371/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Apothecary 20mg THC cannacaps is a high quality, gluten free and soy free product that allows you to get the best THC oil and MTC oil on the market. Providing each patient with a set dosage of 20mg of THC without any hassle. These capsules help patients to battle insomnia and many other health issues they could be experiencing. Just wait 1-2 hours for this product to take effect and experience relaxing bliss.

Ingredients: MTC Oil and CO2 Extracted Lab Tested THC Oil

Dosage: Take 1 capsule, CannaCaps are absorbed by the liver and can take 1-2 hours to take effect and should be taken one at a time to ensure the proper dosing.

&#160;]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img src='http://localhost/wp-content/uploads/2018/03/Apothecary-THC-Oil-20mg-600x600.jpg'></p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
